<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Workshop on HSIEH MENG JU</title><link>https://xmruuu.github.io/tags/workshop/</link><description>Recent content in Workshop on HSIEH MENG JU</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xmruuu.github.io/tags/workshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2023 CAAD Workshop - RhinoVAULT Application</title><link>https://xmruuu.github.io/work/01_bf2023_caad-workshop-rhinovault-application/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xmruuu.github.io/work/01_bf2023_caad-workshop-rhinovault-application/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This workshop introduces the role of digital technology in contemporary architecture, focusing on the development and application of CAD/CAM tools, vibrating knife systems, and CNC technology. Participants will first explore the theoretical foundations, including how these tools transform the architectural design process. They will then gain hands-on experience, from CAD-based part design to operating vibrating knife and CNC machines for model making, working in groups to create small-scale structural prototypes. Finally, the workshop examines real-world cases, current challenges, and future trends, encouraging innovative thinking, critical discussion, and strategies for integrating digital fabrication technologies into architectural practice.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>2022 CAAD Workshop - Microsoft HoloLens</title><link>https://xmruuu.github.io/work/01_bf2023_caad-workshop-microsoft-hololens/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xmruuu.github.io/work/01_bf2023_caad-workshop-microsoft-hololens/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the “HoloLens Glasses Workshop,” we explore the integration of VR technology in construction and design using HoloLens glasses. The workshop offers a hands-on introduction to the HoloLens, showcasing how they transform design and construction processes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants will engage in interactive exercises, experiencing firsthand how VR aids in visualizing architectural designs and enhances project planning in construction. Through practical demonstrations and real-world examples, attendees will see the potential of VR technology in improving accuracy and facilitating collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>2021 CAAD Workshop - KUKA Robotic Arm</title><link>https://xmruuu.github.io/work/01_bf2023_caad-workshop-kuka-robotic-arm-workshop/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xmruuu.github.io/work/01_bf2023_caad-workshop-kuka-robotic-arm-workshop/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the “KUKA Robotic Arm Workshop,” participants will learn to set up and operate a KUKA robotic arm, focusing on essential safety and operational guidelines. The workshop includes an introduction to basic programming, allowing attendees to understand and manipulate the arm’s controls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A key feature of the session is a hands-on exercise in robotic weaving, showcasing the arm’s precision and potential in digital manufacturing and design. This concise yet comprehensive workshop is an ideal introduction to the possibilities of robotic automation in creative and industrial applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>